The One Where It All Began
English Subtitles by
SUOMEN KIELEN MESTARIT INC
Super uplifting great song plays
MAKE SURE YOU CLAP
There's nothing to tell.
It's just some guy I work with.
You're going out with a guy.
There's gotta be something
wrong with him.
So does he have a hump
and a hair piece?
Wait. Does he eat chalk?
I don't want her to go
through what I did with Carl.
Okay, everybody relax.
This is not even a date.
It's just two people going out to
dinner and not having sex.
Sounds like a date to me.
smouldering Jazz interval plays...
I'm in high school,
in the middle of the cafeteria. . .
. . .and I realize I'm totally naked.
I've had that dream.
Then I look down and I realize
there is a phone. . .
. . .there.
-Instead of--
-That's right!
That one, I've never had.
All of a sudden,
the phone starts to ring.
And it turns out it's my mother.
Which is very, very weird
because she never calls me.
Pensive melancholic jazz interval plays
Hi
This guy says, ''Hello,''
I wanna kill myself.
You okay, sweetie?
I feel like someone grabbed my small
intestine, pulled it out of my mouth. . .
-. . .and tied it around my neck.
-Cookie?
Carol moved out today.
-Let me get you some coffee.
-Thanks.
-ew
- No, don't!
Stop cleansing my aura.
Just leave my aura alone, okay?
I'll be fine.
I hope she'll be very happy.
No, you don't.
To hell with her. She left me!
And you never knew she was a lesbian.
NO OK... Why does everyone
keep fixating on that?
She didn't know.
How should I know?
Sometimes I wish I was a lesbian.
Did I say that out loud?
Look, you're feeling
a lot of pain right now.
You're angry. You're hurting.
Can I tell you what
the answer is?
Strip joints!
Come on, you're single.
Have some hormones.
See, but I don't want
to be single, okay?
I just want to be married again.
And I just want a million dollars!
Rachel?
Oh, God, Monica!
Hi! Thank God!
I went to your building and
this guy with a hammer said. . .
. . .that you might be here and you are.
-Can I get you some coffee?
-Decaf.
Everybody, this is Rachel,
another Lincoln High survivor.
This is everybody.
Chandler and Phoebe. . .
. . .and Joey. And remember
my brother, Ross?
Sure!
Umbrella cock blocks Ross
You want to tell us now, or are we
waiting for four wet bridesmaids?
Oh, God! Well, it started about
a half-hour before the wedding.
I was in this room with
all the presents. . .
. . .and I was looking
at this gravy boat.
This really gorgeous
Limoges gravy boat.
When all of a sudden I realize--
Sweet 'N Low?
I realized. . .
. . .I was more turned on by
this gravy boat than by Barry.
And then I really freaked out,
when it hit me:
How much Barry looks like
Mr. Potato Head.
I always knew he looked
familiar, but. . . .
I had to get out of there,
and I started wondering. . .
. . . ''Why am I doing this?''
and ''Who am I doing this for?''
I didn't know where to go, and I know
you and I have drifted apart. . .
. . .but you're the only person
I know in the city.
Who wasn't asked to the wedding.
I was kind of hoping that
wouldn't be an issue.
small jazz interval plays
upbeat guitar builds up the vibe
Corny Spanish telenovela plays in TV
I guess he bought her
the pipe organ. . .
. . .and she's really not
happy about it.
Daddy, I just--
I can't marry him.
I'm sorry.
I just don't love him.
Well, it matters to me!
She should not be
wearing those pants.
I say push her down the stairs!
Push her down the stairs!
Come on, Daddy, listen!
All my life, everyone's
always told me, ''You're a shoe! ''
''You're a shoe! You're a shoe!
You're a shoe! ''
I stopped and said,
''What if I don't wanna be a shoe?
What if I want to be a purse?
Or a hat?''
I don't want you to buy me a hat,
I--
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
You can see where he'd have trouble.
Look, Daddy, it's my life.
Well, maybe I'll just stay
here with Monica.
I guess we've established
she's staying with Monica.
Well, maybe that's my decision.
Well, maybe I don't need your money.
Wait! Wait! I said maybe!
Smooth riffing jazz music plays
A single suggestive note lingers...
Just breathe.
Breathe, that's it.
Just try to think
of nice, calm things.
Raindrops on roses
And whiskers on kittens
Doorbells and sleigh bells
And something with mittens
La la la something
And noodles with string
-These are a--
-I'm all better now.
I helped.
This is probably for
the best, you know?
Independence.
Taking control of your life.
If you need anything,
you can always come to Joey.
Me and Chandler live across the hall.
And he's away a lot.
Joey, stop hitting on her!
It's her wedding day.
What? Like there's
a rule or something?
Please don't do that again.
It's a horrible sound.
It's Paul.
Buzz him in.
-Who's Paul?
-Paul, the wine guy?
Maybe.
Your ''not a real date,''
is with Paul, the wine guy?
He finally asked you out?
YEESSSS!!!
It's a ''Dear Diary'' moment.
Rach, I can cancel.
Oh, God. Please, no.
Go, I'll be fine.
Ross are you okay?
Do you want me to stay?
That'd be good.
-Really?
-Go on! It's Paul, the wine guy!
Hi, come in! Paul, this is. . .
. . .everybody.
Everybody, this is Paul.
-The wine guy.
-I didn't catch your name. Paul?
Change. Sit down.
Two seconds.
I just pulled out four eyelashes.
That can't be good.
Rachel, what are you
up to tonight?
I was supposed to be headed
for Aruba on my honeymoon. . .
. . .so, nothing.
Right. You're not even
getting your honeymoon.
Although, Aruba. This time of year?
Talk about your. . .
. . .big lizards.
If you don't feel
like being alone tonight. . .
. . .Joey and Chandler are
helping me with my furniture.
And we're very excited about it.
Thanks. But I'm just gonna
hang out here.
-It's been a long day.
-Okay. Sure.
Pheebs, wanna help?
I wish I could, but I don't want to.
Riotous jazz run plays as we pan up to the next scene
I'm supposed to attach a bracket-y
thing to the side things. . .
. . .using a bunch of these
little worm guys.
I have no bracket-y thing.
I see no worm guys whatsoever. . .
. . .and I cannot feel my legs.
What's this?
-I have no idea.
-Done with the bookcase.
-All finished.
This was Carol's favorite beer.
She always drank it out of the can.
I should have known.
Let me ask you a question.
She got the furniture,
the stereo, the good TV.
What did you get?
You guys.
-You got screwed.
-Oh, my God.
-I know. I'm such an idiot.
I should've caught on when she went to
the dentist four and five times a week.
I mean, how clean can teeth get?
My brother's going through that.
He's a mess.
How did you get through it?
He might try accidentally breaking
something valuable of hers.
-Say her--
-Leg?
That's one way of going through it.
Me, I went for the watch.
You actually broke her watch?
Barry, I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
You probably think it's about making
love with your socks on, but it isn't.
It's about me.
And I just--
Machine cut me off again.
Anyway. . . .
You know what's scary? What if there
is only one woman for everybody?
I mean, what if you get one
woman, and that's it?
Unfortunately, in my case,
there was only one woman for her.
What are you talking about?
One woman.
That's like saying there's only
one flavor of ice cream for you.
Let me tell you something.
There's lots of flavors out there.
Rocky road, and cookie dough,
and bing cherry vanilla.
You can get them with jimmies,
or nuts, or whipped cream.
This is the best thing that
ever happened to you!
You got married. You were
like, what? Eight?
Welcome back to the world.
Grab a spoon!
I honestly don't know
if I'm hungry or horny.
Then stay out of my freezer.
Ever since she
walked out on me, I. . . .
What? What?
You wanna spell it out with noodles?
It's more of a fifth date
kind of revelation.
So there's going to be a fifth date?
Isn't there?
Yeah, yeah. I think there is.
What were you going to say?
Ever since she left me. . .
. . .I haven't been able to perform. . .
. . .sexually.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
I'm so sorry.
Being spit on is probably
not what you need right now.
How long?
Two years.
I'm glad you smashed her watch.
So you still think you might
want that fifth date?
Yeah, I do.
CORNY MOVIE PLAYING
But Joanie loved Chachi.
That's the difference.
''Grab a spoon. ''
Do you know long it's been
since I grabbed a spoon?
Do the words, ''Billy, don't be a
hero,'' mean anything to you?
You know, here's the thing. Even if
I could get it together enough. . .
. . .to ask a woman out. . .
. . .who am I going to ask?
Mushy 90s pop plays as Rachel looks super sad
PART 2 WILL PROBABLY COME ...
...AT SOME POINT
www.tvsubtitles.net